everyone is applied now but it's just only for a stall listing there's always
privacy tab and distribution by default you can obviously select which
countries have to be distributed i will select all of them which is by default
it will be visible to everyone and it's free of charge but we can specify
like container per case well for now it's free of charge there's a
some test instructions and it's just basically for people who want to test it
out upon verifying neural crop waste ifs
because people will verify your crop extensions so you have to give them
additional instructions and credential and last thing would we have to do we
have to fill up the privacy so like a single purpose
so single purpose description must establish one clear single purpose
description for your extension so for instance for us it might be
right if you allow us to search across all of the such engines
categories by country there's permission justification like for every
pension you request such as active or type you need to state
why you actually need it if there is a carry mode code
because if you're including an JavaScript file or other types of scripts that
are not contained within your extension folder like for
example calling jQuery externally you must state this
and justify why you need to use that external code
otherwise and shawl scripts are included locally in the folder
there is a data collection so you must explicitly state exactly
would data you are collecting from users for example if you wanted to
collect the users behaviors to personalize the display of the search
engines in my case and you would need to state this
and data selling as well and justification we have data usage here
but if you don't trust for anything we can always try to
and submit this is privacy policy URL on exception must have privacy
police if it collects data so we have to apply
like other zero so for this case as you can see for
package we have to apply this is like a status this is privacy
we have to go for it so i now i can just go for here
and regarding that i would just open a new agent and we can switch to
ask and i will ask for it so now
help me to answer this
it will now reveal all the files we have a JavaScript
and this has 1000s so i can use
and now a context manager's notification script you might
get my notification and this free ones oh yeah
now we have to make now we have to see the permission
and I need to answer the context
menu justification scripting justification
and active tab justification
and under ru using remote code justification
now we'll chat with our code for a little bit
so i can copy here
active tab i'll just copy it as well
as scripting this is one and a context menu
okay and now when we don't have anything
so i'm not using remote code sorry but still
be the okay we don't need some extra contracts to your but
pretty fine pattern so we don't need to remote code
that's the usage i will save it there's privacy policy euro
can ask it
it asks for privacy policy euro
is there numbers for it
and that we can create our own one but i know there are some creators so we can
speed up our process
you still have this hasn't changed anything
and now we can use some of the extension here
press no no no
now i'll just go this one in my email
i'll go next step now
you'll next step now we'll just generate
and you'll receive this voice it is in address
it'll be a three
okay it will be Tim's feet actually we can paste it over as well
so i will go to my privacy because this one allows us to
it's actually nice start-up idea to have privacy for it
now just go for it i'll just paste it i'll save us a draw
we have our own ideas well and now we can see if i rank it's ready
we have to add an email so just add a verify my email
and i will just verify it
so now i will just get the verification
now it is press verification this is the id it's very five now
and if i go back now to my items and see here
i think it should work it's seven for review that's great so now it will
first and we press seven for review and before we actually apply
a new generate ai code i think it's still great to
call across all of the files that you have added and change
we see some of his stuff with an extension
and maybe apply it right okay so this one
i will call to search engines you have to basically understand maybe
it disclosed some code so always check an i generated code
this is actually pretty simple because it just changed the query for the one
that i have applied but i think it's still great to check okay this works
so now i can press submit for review and i will go
it's submitting item we have to wait a little bit
and your extension was submitted for review
and we need to wait around the month sometimes it's quicker
so now if we go to my developer dashboard we see it's pending review
and then we'll be able to check writing users and all of the details because
when you go there obviously you have access to analytics when you can see
installs, own installs, impressions, users and
ratings for your Chrome extension